!
They called him the.
I look up.
to the stars.
and reach for the sky.
I believe.
in tomorrow.
if we try.
ııı ıí? H!
C'mon, let's go everybody.
Let me share the music.
C'mon, let's go baby, baby.
Let me share the one dream.
C'mon, let's go everybody.
Let me share the good times.
We share the good times.
Come on, let's go.
Baby, baby, oh, we share the one world.
It's hard to see for you and me.
Through the darkness
that is in this world.
So hard to see or to believe.
In where we need to go.
Yes, you and me, it's true that we.
Feel the rush brought up by this world.
Through head to feet, I feel the beat.
Getting me to walk on, oh yeah.
Share the music, no matter what.
Share the one dream, believe in yourself.
Share the good times, take my eye now.
Share the one world now.
I look up to the stars
and reach for the sky.
No matter what, I'll
try no matter how high.
So let us go beyond, far and wide.
I believe in tomorrow if we try.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Come on, let's go, everybody.
Oh, we share the music.
We share the music.
Come on, let's go, baby, baby.
Oh, we share the one world? No!
Oh, as we chase, we're being chased.
From the top we go on straight and wild.
We're on our way, I've got to say.
Hey, I want to share your style.
Now here it starts, so don't lose heart.
They're bound to lose to this flavor.
From boot to hood, I feel so good.
I will be free to be, oh yeah.
Share the music, even if I.
Share the one dream, I know where you are.
Share the good times,
share the one world now.
I look up to the stars.
And reach for the sky.
No matter what.
I'll try no matter how high.
So let us go.
Beyond, far and wide.
I believe in tomorrow.
If we try.
I know that you are there.
Just on the other side.
Wait there for me.
Soon it will be you and I.
Then let us go.
Beyond, far and wide.
I believe in the one world.
If we try.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Come on, let's go, everybody.
Oh, we share the music.
Come on, let's go, baby, baby.
Oh, we share the one world.
And ever since.
I've always wanted to meet you, Luffy.
And see the spirited boy for myself.
Aw, Shanks.
But I can't in good
conscience talk about things
involving Shanks that he
hasn't mentioned yet himself.
In any case, you've done
well to make it this far.
I'm sure Shanks is eagerly awaiting
your arrival in the new world.
Really?
Do you think so?
Man, I can't wait to see him.
Now then, getting down to business.
I believe you wanted
your ship coated, right?
Then it's high time for me
to return to my real work.
You!
That reminds me.
I wasn't sure exactly how
much the coating would cost.
Ah, don't you worry about it, Hachi.
I couldn't possibly take
money from friends of yours.
Oh, wow!
You're the best, Rayleigh!
Not sure why, but he's doing it for free!
Thanks!
We certainly appreciate it.
That's very generous of you.
Rayleigh.
Hmm?
I have a question.
What exactly is the will of D?
There was a Poneglyph on Sky Island.
Roger's name was inscribed on it.
In that ancient form of
writing, how does he know it?
How can he use that language?
I made it here.
And I will guide this passage all the
way to the farthest ends of the earth.
Pirate Gold D Roger.
Please tell me?
Did you learn what happened to the
world during the Blank Century?
The missing history from 900 years ago?
Yes,
we know.
We learned all of it.
The entirety of the missing history.
But miss, you mustn't be so hasty.
Just keep moving forward. See?
This is your journey now.
We and Ohara might have hurried
too much for our own good.
I'm sure that's not
what you wanted to hear.
Even if I told you everything you wanted
to know about that history here and now,
just as you are, you couldn't
do anything about it.
Once you've taken the time
to really see the world,
it might change your outlook and
possibly lead you to a different answer.
But if you still insist on hearing
it, I can tell you everything.
It's up to you.
No, I'll pass.
Then continue my journey.
It'll all make sense to
you one of these days.
I'm very sorry for what happened
in your homeland of Ohara.
But that doesn't change the fact that
Roger didn't decipher that writing.
We were all pirates, remember?
Not geniuses or scholars.
No match for Clover or the
other great minds of Ohara.
See, Captain Roger just heard
the voice of the universe?
And that's all that happened.
Are you sure about this, Robin?
Seems like you're passing
up a pretty big opportunity.
Hey, old guy, I've got
a question of my own.
The treasure Roger talked
about, the legendary One Piece.
Tell me, is it really...
It's enough!
I don't want to know where
the One Piece is hidden.
I don't even want to know if it exists.
Every single one of us
put our life on the line
and set out to sea
without knowing anything.
I'd rather give up being
a pirate than know.
I won't go on a boring adventure.
We need to sail and
find out for ourselves.
Sorry, sorry. I knew that.
It just slipped out of
my mouth, that's all.
I don't want to know either.
I just remembered. I have...
I'll die if I learn anything
about the One Piece disease.
Don't say anything, old guy.
You'll kill me.
Keep it to yourself.
Oh, in that case, let me ask you.
Do you think you can do it?
The new world far surpasses
anything you can imagine.
Your foes will be powerful.
Knowing that, do you still think
you can rule this mighty sea?
What I don't want to rule
anything being king of
the pirates is about being
more free than anyone.
I see
Monkey D Luffy
I must say I like your
style your ship is in
Grove number one right.
I guess I'll head over
there now and get started
what do you plan to do
anyway at any moment an?
Admiral could be here looking for you.
That's right.
We'll only be a nuisance if we stay here.
So maybe we go shopping.
What? Are you insane?
We're being chased by
the world government.
We've got to hide.
He's got a point.
If we stick together, that makes us
an easy target for those Marines.
And it'll be easier for the
old guy to finish his work
if we each find somewhere to
lay low in town for a while.
Right.
Then I say we split up,
keep track of the work, and when
it's done, we meet back here.
Who is that guy strategizing over there?
Because it's not Zoro.
Hey, Chaka, we have any cards?
Yes, I believe there's one left.
Whoa, this is a Vibra card!
You know what it is?
That simplifies things.
Since I happen to be a
bit notorious myself,
I think I'll move your ship from Grove No.
1 and work on it somewhere more secluded.
I'll need three days to
complete the coding process.
Why does it take so long?
It needs time to seal so
I can't go any faster.
Then it's three days of
survival in the woods for us!
Oh, scary.
Let's meet at sundown three days from now.
I don't know what grove I'll be on then,
so use the beaver cards to find me.
Wherever it leads you,
that will be the place where I'll be
finishing the coding and waiting for you.
It's probably a good idea
for you to pick up some
supplies for your underwater
voyage to Fishman Island.
Luffy, all of you, thank
you for everything.
You guys are awesome.
And I'm sorry.
Sorry I caused you guys so much trouble.
I owe you my life.
We'll show you the way to Fishman
Island, don't worry about a thing,
so do your best to stay
clear of the marines.
Hachi, get plenty of bed rest, okay?
See you again in three days.
We'll be there to send you off.
See you later, nice lady.
We're up against an admiral.
We need to make sure
none of us gets killed.
Stop saying scary stuff like that!
Three days, huh?
Let's all go to the amusement park!
Be careful yeah take care of
yourselves we will you do the same
I suppose I should be off too
It's been a whirlwind ever
since we got here but I
wasn't expecting to run
into Roger's vice-captain.
I'm kind of stunned.
Huh?
I mean, what are the odds?
He's a pretty intimidating
guy for an old geezer.
I'll give him that much.
Well, he is the most famous man in
Roger's crew, and deservedly so it seems.
So that's what crewmen on the
Odo Jackson were like, huh?
Giving a hand to that Roger guy
is something I'll never forget.
Man, I'm glad I got to meet him. You know,
I never would have pegged you for someone
who had such reverence for your elders.
Yeah?
Well, sometimes I do, okay?
Now shut the hell up!
Hey!
I've got an idea!
Let's go to the amusement park!
Bad idea!
Sounds like fun!
Not you two!
It's Admiral Kizaru!
We gotta get the hell out of here!
Don't let those pirates escape!
Hello there are wanted men
everywhere on this archipelago.
Look out for the ones
worth over 100 million
Hello
This is Admiral Kizaru
Hmm, that's odd
Well, that's awful strange
No, hold on,
there's still a chance I think I can get
the drop on him and
take him down from here.
And if I do, I'll be famous. Huh?
Are you out of your damn mind?
This is one of the strongest guys
in the Marines we're talking about.
Now take this! No, wait, stop!
Hello?
What the hell?
I know I didn't miss him that time.
The bullet passed right through his head.
Oh, so terribly odd.
He's obviously got some kind
of crazy Devil Fruit powers.
Guns aren't going to work on him.
Run for it!
Pardon me, but I was wondering
if you could help me out.
I'm here looking for a man
named Sentomaru, you see?
He's a subordinate of
mine. Do you know him?
Gee, all I did was ask him a question.
Oh, my God.
I think Admiral Kizaru
went a hair overboard.
He does better than to break
the hustle muscle mangroves.
Oh, wow.
I forget my own strength sometimes.
Talk about crazy.
That's Admiral Kizaru, I take it.
Please, Apoo, this is
dangerous for us, too.
We really need to get out of here.
You fool.
What fun is there in slinking away?
It's better to run after
you've pissed your enemy off.
Then what are you planning to do?
We're questing backup at the harbor!
What's wrong?
I don't know how, and I don't know why,
but all the soldiers have
turned into kids and old people!
What the hell's going on?
My own back!
Perfect!
She's the one that did this.
It was jewelry bonnie.
She's got a bounty of 140 million.
I know you.
You're capone gang bang and you've
got 138 million berry bounty. No way.
You're sailing out of here.
What did your crew run off and leave you?
Too bad for you.
Hands in the air.
Ha!
In terms of tough, guys.
You boys are outmatched.
Ooh, excuse me, but I was wondering
if you fellas could help me out.
Let's Kizaru!
We'll keep him busy for
you, Captain. Please, sir.
You need to get out of here.
No need to panic.
I won't be dying today.
But the best place to hide
is in the amusement park.
You're so full of it.
You just want to screw
around and have fun.
Who is this guy?
Enemy attack!
Hurry up, go!
Commence the attack!
Get those cannons ready!
Open the gunplots!
Commence bombardment! What?
Fire!
What?
This is crazy!
Something is flying out of his chest!
What the hell just happened?
Didn't even have to lift a finger!
Hey, look at his stomach!
Something's coming out.
I don't know how that.
The power works, but I think I'm starting
to see why they call him the gang.
Firing squad, take aim!
Watch with the smoke!
Potter, take it easy, it's too much!
Told ya, you'll need
more troops than that.
Get outta here!
One of the seven warlords
has joined the attack.
Wait, are you serious?
Which one of them is it?
A warlord.
I guess it was too much to ask
to sneak past Navy headquarters.
How unfortunate!
My pride won't let me walk away.
Captain, please, you must escape.
It's far too dangerous here.
Captain Hawkins, what are you...
Combat.
Chance of defeat, 100%.
Pardon, but could you help me?
Escape.
Chance of success, 12%.
I'm looking for a man named Sentomaru.
Do you know him?
Defense, chance of evasion, 76%.
I know of no such man.
Go ask someone else.
Well, if I can't find him, that leaves
me with a bit of spare time, you see.
And if I have some spare time, I
obviously can't let a wanted man escape.
Especially one with a 249 million berry
bounty magician Basil Hawken speed is
weight observe This is what it feels
like to be kicked at the speed of light?
What?
Captain!
What the? What happened?
Are we under attack? I don't know.
He just suddenly went flying.
Look at that. He's strong.
Hey, wait, what's he doing now?
I didn't see anyone.
He just burst into flames.
Who attacked? And from where?
What was that impressive you far
surpassed what I imagined now ain't
that weird to think Two would be
destroyed already against an admiral
such as yourself I might feel nervous
Even with ten
hold
on
is that the
mad monk Arouge and he's not alone
either that's Bartholome I am you, Kuma,
one of the seven warlords of the sea.
You're strong.
I'll give you that much.
Kizaru! No!
How unfortunate.
I have a navy admiral ahead
of me, and a warlord behind.
I'm finished!
Not necessarily.
I don't see the shadow of death upon you.
Oh?
Is that so?
Hawkins of the North Blue.
Heh, thanks for the tip,
foe though you may be.
Oh good, it looks like someone
else decided to join the fight.
Is that...
Red Flag Diaz Drake, why's he here?
Rear Admiral Drake.
Ah crap, I hadn't planned
on running into Kizaru.
I've taken quite a beating.
But let's see if Hawkins'
prediction is true or not.
There might be some hope for me yet.
Let's start this over nice and slow.
Look at this!
This is insane! Unbelievable!
I've got blast here!
You're insane!
Whoever stays here is gonna die!
This is our chance to escape.
Ah, you're no fun.
We're here to party, and
that's Captain's orders.
Who the heck are you?
Get back, Luffy.
He's one of the seven
warlords of the sea. He is?
How do you guys know that?
Luffy, don't let that attack hit you.
It's a shockwave.
Throw, what is that? Great.
So, he can do this crap too?
Hey, you lied, that wasn't a shockwave.
That was a beam!
You're gonna be impressed
straight to your grave.
Bartholomew Comane, why are you here?
That bastard.
Hey, I remember him now.
He's the guy that showed up at
Thriller Park I never fought.
That's right, the very same.
Things got pretty dicey
when he started shooting
at us with shockwaves and
the paws on his hands.
We barely made it out alive.
The fact that we are still alive is
probably the reason he came back.
In other words, we got lucky last
time, but he's here to finish the job.
Sure, that's one way to look at it.
But I call this payback time.
Who did?
You got him.
Not exactly.
Reef.
All right, second gear.
We know he's strong, no question.
So let's go all out from the start.
I'll be on the boat.
Something's off here he seems
different from the last time we met.
Let's go.
What's taking so long the warship
should have been here by now?
Why hasn't uncle keezaryu
contacted me yet?
It's chaos already.
He'd better hurry.
Or there won't be any rookies left.
Not at this rate.